<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wuyan</string>
    <string name="app_title">5 new ways to enjoy music</string>
    <string name="thing_1_content">For when your favorite song just isn\'t long enough\nThis web app lets you upload a favorite MP3 and will then generate a never-ending and ever changing version of the song. Infinite Jukebox uses the Echo Nest analyzer to break the song into beats. It plays the song beat by beat, but at every beat there\'s a chance that it will jump to a different part of song that happens to sound very similar to the current beat. For beat similarity the uses pitch, timbre, loudness, duration and the position of the beat within a bar. There\'s a nifty visualization that shows all the possible transitions that can occur at any beat. Built at Music Hack Day Boston 2012.</string>
    <string name="thing_2_content">Some songs just need a little bit of Bonzo\nThis app will take a track and re-render it as if John Bonham of Led Zepplin was the drummer. This app works by cutting songs up into beats and tatums, and aligning the beats to John Bonham Drum patterns.</string>
    <string name="thing_3_content">Lots of flying cubes!\nA dynamic visualization of the Ellie Goulding song, syncrhonized with The Echo Nest data. </string>
    <string name="thing_4_content">Don\'t just play your music, play with your music\nGirl Talk in a Box lets you interact with your favorite song. You can speed it up, slow it down, skip beats, play it backwards, beat by beat. You can make it swing. You can make breaks and drops. You can upload your own song or select a song from the gallery. The Echo Nest analyzer is used to break the song into beats and tatums that are displayed as colored tiles that you can interact with. Built at MIDEM Music Hack Day 2013.</string>
    <string name="thing_5_content">Create a mixtape of local artists for your roadtrip\nRoadtrip Mixtape is an application that you can use to create road trip playlists. Type in the name of your starting and ending points, and the application will create a playlist of music by artists that from the area you are traveling through. Drive through Boston you might hear Aerosmith or Donna Summer. Drive through New Orleans and you might hear Lil Wayne or Dr. John. The application uses the Echo Nest API to get the artist location data for thousands of artists.</string>
</resources>